# **AN NGUYEN**

Full Stack Developer

### About me

As a research scientist, I have spent the last 10 years trying to develop cures for diseases that afflict humans. I've always followed my passion and consequently I always aim for excellence in my career.

I am now applying my experience in project management, communication and critical thinking as a full stack web developer. I tackle new challenges with grit determination and always with a smile on my face.

I am an Australian Citizen with full rights to work in Australia.

### Contact



12/159 Hawkesbury Rd, Westmead, Sydney, 2145



annguyen@sydney.edu.au

github/pleathershaman

https://pleathershaman.github.io

### Education

<b>The Web Developer Bootcamp</b> Udemy	2018 - 2019
<b>The Modern React Bootcamp</b> Udemy	2019 - 2019
Master of Science University of Sydney	2011 - 2012

### Experience

## Molecular Imaging Scientist

2012 - 2018

#### ANSTO

ANSTO is Australia's primary research facility for nuclear science. In this position, managed and contributed to research projects that use nuclear imaging. I was independently running multiple projects concurrently and was the main point of contact for all correspondence and communication. I was also responsible for organising project-related administration such as contracts, budgets, regulatory compliance and non-disclosure agreements.

#### **Research Assistant**

2008 - 2011

#### The Save Sight Institute

My main role in this position develop new experiments to investigate the causes of a rare eye disease. In this position, I set up a pipeline for analysing the differences in protein levels in a disease model.

### Skills

HTML5	••••		css	••••
WordPress	••••		JavaScript	••••
React	••••		Git/Github	••••
Image Processing				
SEO Optimisation				
Problem Solvi	ing	•••	••	
Project Mana	gement	•••	••	
Communication	on	•••	• •	

### **Awards**

The Wenkart Foundation Grant A competitive scholarship valued at \$28,000 p.a. (AUD) awarded for Master of Science.

### References

Dr. Arvind Parmar (PhD)
Imaging Physiologist
ANSTO
Arvind@ansto.gov.au

Dr. Ivan Greguric (PhD)
Head of Radiochemistry
ANSTO
Ivan.Greguric@ansto.gov.au

### **Personal Projects**

#### Kitchen Catalogue

Kitchen Catalogue is an online database that allows users to create, edit and organise their cooking recipes. It features a full-stack MERN application with connection to a RESTful API, email confirmation and password reset. Technologies used include, React, Redux, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6+.

Link: http://kitchencatalogue.theaspiringwebdeveloper.com

Code: https://github.com/PleatherShaman/KitchenCatalogue

#### **React Color Picker**

React Color Picker is a single-page react application that helps users design their own color palettes and view different shades of a particular color. This application was the cap-stone projects of the Udemy Modern React Bootcamp. Technologies used include, React, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6+.

Link: https://reactcolorpicker.herokuapp.com/

Code: https://github.com/PleatherShaman/reactColorPicker

#### **Inspiration Montage**

Inspiration Montage is a small react application that shows users a photo gallery based in their search terms. Featuring an infinite scroll and connection to the Unsplashed API, this program provides the user with visual inspiration on nearly every topic. Technologies used include, React, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6+.

Link: https://inspirationmontage.herokuapp.com/

Code: https://github.com/PleatherShaman/InspirationMontage